Guide to the John Henry and Anna Botsford Comstock papers, 1833-1955,
Comstock, John Henry and Anna Botsford papers,
- Correspondence
  - John Henry Comstock professional correspondence
    - M-R
      - Rolfe, Henry Winchester, 1889-10-17 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Rombrake, P.O., 1891-04-18 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Romeike, Henry, Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
        pressclipping bar
      - Root, Amos Ives, 1886-05-28 (Box 2, Folder 13)
        Apiarist
      - Root, Amos Ives, 1886-08-24 (Box 2, Folder 16)
      - Root, Amos Ives, 1887-01-13 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Root, Amos Ives, 1887-04-19 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Root, Amos Ives, 1887-05-19 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Root, Amos Ives, 1888-11-06 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - Root, Amos Ives, 1892-08-12 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Root, Amos Ives, Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Root, E.R., 1886-04-16 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - Root, E.R., 1886-04-22 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - Root, E.R., 1886-04-30 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - Root, James A., 1886-05-13 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Root, Lyman C., 1886-07-19 (Box 2, Folder 15)
        Bee-keeping authority
      - Root, Lyman C., 1886-08-06 (Box 2, Folder 16)
      - Rose, J.F., 1886-05-17 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Rose, J.F., 1886-06-08 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - Rose, J.F., 1887-05-30 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Rose, J.F., 1891-05-14 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Rose, J.F., 1891-05-23 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Ross, A., 1890-12-22 (Box 4, Folder 6)
        bill for woodwork
      - Ross, Marie Stuart, 1892-04-11 (Box 5, Folder 7)
        Mrs. James T. Wolcott; teacher
      - Rossel, William J., 1891-12-16 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Rothe, Jenny, Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Rothrock, Joseph Trimble, 1890-01-06 (Box 3, Folder 18)
        Professor of Botany
      - Rothrock, Joseph Trimble, 1890-01-16 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - Rothrock, Joseph Trimble, 1890-05-26 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - Rothschild Brothers, 1890-04-01 (Box 3, Folder 21)
        Department Store
      - Rothschild Brothers, 1890-04-19 (Box 3, Folder 21)
      - Rothschild Brothers, 1890-07-01 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Rothschild Brothers, 1891-01-01 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Rothschild Brothers, 1891-11-27 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Rothschild Brothers, 1892-12-10 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Rothschild Brothers, 1892-12-17 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Rothschild Brothers, 1893-04-21 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      - Rothschild Brothers, 1894-02-06 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Rothschild Brothers, Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Rouzand, Dr. H., 1892-07-22 (Box 5, Folder 10)
        in French
      - Royall, T.E., 1890-08-09 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Rude, H., 1891-01-10 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Rumsey and Company, C.J., 1888-10-30 (Box 3, Folder 3)
        Hardware
      - Rumsey and Company, C.J., 1888-11-13 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - Rumsey and Company, C.J., 1889-02-02 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - Rumsey and Company, C.J., 1889-02-22 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - Rumsey and Company, C.J., 1889-03-25 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - Rumsey, William Earl, 1890-07-31 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Rumsey, William Earl, 1890-08-28 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Rumsey, William Earl, 1890-09-25 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Rumsey, William Earl, 1891-08-06 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Rumsey, William Earl, 1891-08-22 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Rumsey, William Earl, 1892-02-22 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Rumsey, William Earl, 1892-06-01 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Rumsey, William Earl, 1892-06-29 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Rumsey, William Earl, 1892-08-02 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Rumsey, William Earl, 1892-09-29 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Runney, C.J. and Company, 1891-01-06 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Runyon, Frank Willits, 1892-08-30 (Box 5, Folder 11)
        The Plainfield Courier, Ed. and Pub.
      - Rural New Yorker, 1889-05-18 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Rural Publishing Company, 1892-06-25 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Rural Publishing Company, 1892-07-21 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Rural Publishing Company, 1892-07-27 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Russel, William Channing, 1891-12-31 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Russell, Edward C., 1890-09-22 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Russell, Ernest Emory, 1890-11-14 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Russell, Frank Downing, 1890-06-30 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - Russell, Frank Downing, 1890-07-17 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Russell, James Earl, 1889-09-30 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - Russell, James Earl, 1889-10-30 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Russell, James Earl, 1890-11-09 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Russell, Theresa A., 1890-09-13 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Ryan, Francis G., 1888-09-25 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - Ryan, Francis G., 1888-10-13 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Ryder, John A., 1887-10-19 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Ryder, John A., 1887-11-11 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - S-Z
      - Sage, William H., 1889-11-04 (Box 3, Folder 16)
        receipt for contribution to CUAA
      - Salmon, Saniel Elmer, 1892-05-26 (Box 5, Folder 8)
        Bureau of Animal Industry
      - Sanatorium, The, 1889-08-17 (Box 3, Folder 13)
        Hygenic Institue
      - Sanatorium, The, 1889-08-26 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - Sanatorium, The, 1889-08-31 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - Sanatorium, The, 1889-09-07 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - Sanatorium, The, 1889-09-14 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - Sanatorium, The, 1889-09-16 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - Sanborn, F.G., 1881-11-05 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Sanderson, Ezra Dwight, 1898-09-12 (Box 6, Folder 17)
        Professor of Entomology
      - Sanderson, Ezra Dwight, 1898-10-23 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - Sanderson, Ezra Dwight, 1899-04-10 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Sandrock, George, 1888-04-07 (Box 2, Folder 29)
        insect information
      - Sangster, C.H., 1890-12-15 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Sargent and Greenleaf, 1888-06-07 (Box 2, Folder 31)
        locksmith
      - Sargent and Greenleaf, 1888-08-11 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - Sargent and Greenleaf, 1888-12-06 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - Sargent and Greenleaf, 1890-06-21 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - Sasaki, A., 1894-03-30 (Box 6, Folder 7)
        Professor, Agricultural College
        Tokyo, Japan
      - Saum, John L., 1892-01-30 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Saunders, George S., 1886-05-10 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Saunders, George S., 1892-04-11 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Saunders, William E., 1883-01-20 (Box 2, Folder 2)
        Entomological Society of Ontario
      - Saunders, William E., 1887-12-20 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Saunders, William E., 1888-04-12 (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Saunders, William E., 1888-06-14 (Box 2, Folder 31)
      - Scaife, Charles Cooke, 1888-07-09 (Box 2, Folder 32)
      - Scaife, James Verner, 1888-06-06 (Box 2, Folder 31)
        son of Charles Cook Scaife
      - Schaeffer, Charles A., 1890-09-18 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Schaeffer, Charles A., 1890-09-29 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Scharff, Adolph, 1889-05-31 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Schnellendruessler, H., 1889-06-26 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Schnellendruessler, H., 1889-06-29 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Schonborn, Henry F., 1891-09-16 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - Schroder, Chr., 1899-02-28 (Box 6, Folder 19)
        in German
      - Schulte, JGW, Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Schulz, Waldemar, 1898-12-08 (Box 6, Folder 18)
      - Schurman, Jacob Gould, 1892-05-24 (Box 5, Folder 8)
        President of Cornell 1892-1920
      - Schurman, Jacob Gould, 1892-05-30 (Box 5, Folder 8)
        President of Cornell 1892-1921
      - Schurman, Jacob Gould, 1892-06-11 (Box 5, Folder 9)
        President of Cornell 1892-1922
      - Schurman, Jacob Gould, 1893-01-10 (Box 5, Folder 16)
        President of Cornell 1892-1923
      - Schurman, Jacob Gould, 1893-04-08 (Box 5, Folder 17)
        President of Cornell 1892-1924
      - Schurman, Jacob Gould, 1898-12-15 (Box 6, Folder 18)
        President of Cornell 1892-1925
      - Schurman, Jacob Gould, Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
        President of Cornell 1892-1926
      - Schwarz, E.A., 1891-11-07 (Box 5, Folder 1)
        Entomological Society of Washington
      - Schwarz, E.A., 1894-04-20 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Science, Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Scott, Orion C., 1886-03-09 (Box 2, Folder 11)
        Principal, Oskaloosa Public Schools, Iowa
      - Scott, R., 1889-01-16 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - Scribner's, Charles Sons, 1891-08-15 (Box 4, Folder 14)
        Publishers and Booksellers, NY
      - Scribner's, Charles Sons, 1892-09-01 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Scudder, Samuel Hubbard, 1885-10-18 (Box 2, Folder 7)
        Naturalist
      - Scudder, Samuel Hubbard, 1886-04-06 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - Scudder, Samuel Hubbard, 1886-05-02 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Scudder, Samuel Hubbard, 1886-10-13 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - Scudder, Samuel Hubbard, 1887-02-14 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Scudder, Samuel Hubbard, 1887-05-04 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Scudder, Samuel Hubbard, 1887-05-09 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Scudder, Samuel Hubbard, 1887-12-09 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Scudder, Samuel Hubbard, 1888-12-04 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - Scudder, Samuel Hubbard, 1888-12-23 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - Scudder, Samuel Hubbard, 1890-01-10 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - Scudder, Samuel Hubbard, 1890-07-16 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Scudder, Samuel Hubbard, 1893-05-14 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - Scudder, Samuel Hubbard, 1894-03-04 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Scudder, Samuel Hubbard, 1894-03-10 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Scudder, Samuel Hubbard, 1894-03-18 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Seafield, E.H., 1896-10-19 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Seaman, Charles S., 1890-01-01 (Box 3, Folder 18)
        Hack and Livery Stable
      - Seaman, Charles S., 1891-01-01 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Seaman, Charles S., 1894-01-01 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Seaman, D.J. and Son, 1885-10-21 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Seaman, D.J. and Son, 1886-05-31 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Seaman, D.J. and Son, 1886-12 (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - Seaman, D.J. and Son, 1887-04-01 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Seaman, D.J. and Son, 1887-08-06 (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - Seaman, D.J. and Son, 1889-01-01 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - Seaman, James, 1886-06-26 (Box 2, Folder 14)
        bills for carpentry work
      - Seaman, James, 1888-02-22 (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Seaman, James, Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Seamon Brothers, 1899-04-10 (Box 6, Folder 19)
        Clothiers and Furnishers
      - Seamon Brothers, 1899-04-12 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Sears, D.E., 1886-07-29 (Box 2, Folder 15)
        Ithaca Steam Laundry
      - Sears, D.E., 1886-10-01 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - Sears, D.E., 1888-06-01 (Box 2, Folder 31)
      - Sears, D.E., 1889-10-12 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Sears, D.E., 1889-10-16 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Sears, D.E., 1890-06-02 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - Sears, D.E., 1890-12-19 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Sears, D.E., 1891-04-20 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Sears, D.E., 1891-12-21 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Sears, D.E., 1892-03-17 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Seaton, Frances, 1899-11-20 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Seaton, Frances, 1899-11-25 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Sedgwick, William T., 1887-02-25 (Box 2, Folder 21)
        American Society of Naturalists
      - Seeber, Ernest, 1892-05-23 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Seeber, Ernest, 1892-05-30 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Seeber, Ernest, 1892-06-06 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Severance, Frank Hayward, 1887-02-07 (Box 2, Folder 21)
        Buffalo Express newspaper
      - Severance, Frank Hayward, Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Sgastade, G., 1899-01-25 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Sharrock, R., 1887-09-21 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Shartle, Robert Alexander, 1890-04-23 (Box 3, Folder 21)
      - Shaw, Albert Morton, 1886-05-18 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Shaw, Albert Morton, 1886-05-25 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Shaw, Albert Morton, 1887-01-06 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Shearer, James Buchanan, 1888-06-29 (Box 2, Folder 31)
      - Shearer, James Buchanan, 1888-07-11 (Box 2, Folder 32)
      - Shearer, James Buchanan, 1889-06-11 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Shearer, James Buchanan, 1890-11-12 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Sheldon, E.A., 1889-05-03 (Box 3, Folder 10)
        State Normal School
      - Sheldon, E.A., 1893-03-22 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      - Sheldon, E.A., 1893-04-15 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      - Sheldon, E.M., 1889-06-17 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Shenessey, William, 1890-04-09 (Box 3, Folder 21)
        The Mercantile and Financial Times; City Editor
      - Shepard and Dudley, 1889-11-02 (Box 3, Folder 16)
        surgical instruments
      - Shepard, Frank William, 1886-07-08 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - Shepard, Frank William, 1889-08-28 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - Shepard, Frank William, 1890-10-13 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Shepard, Frank William, 1891-02-08 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Shepard, Frank William, 1891-07-09 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Shepard, Frank William, 1892-02-06 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Sheppard, George Scott, 1886-08-19 (Box 2, Folder 16)
      - Sherman, Frankling Jr., 1900-07-15 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Sherman, John D. Jr., 1893-11-02 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Sherman, John D. Jr., 1894-11-20 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Sherwood, C.R., 1893-01-02 (Box 5, Folder 16)
        Men's clothing store
      - Shriver, Joseph Alexis, 1891-07-09 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Sias, A.W., 1891-08-22 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Sibley, Edwin Henry, 1886-05-24 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Signoret, 1883-05-09 (Box 2, Folder 2)
        French
      - Siles, William, 1892-03-26 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Simmons, Parke Edmund, 1891-10-01 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Simmons, Parke Edmund, 1891-12-08 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Simonds, Frederic William, 1886-11-04 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - Simonds, Frederic William, 1888-03-20 (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - Simonds, Frederic William, 1890-11-28 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Simonds, Frederic William, 1891-04-30 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Simpson, Crawford and Simpson, 1885-11-19 (Box 2, Folder 8)
        Dry and Fancy Goods; bills
      - Simpson, Crawford and Simpson, 1886-01-25 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Simpson, Crawford and Simpson, 1886-02-23 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - Simpson, Crawford and Simpson, 1886-03-12 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Simpson, Crawford and Simpson, 1886-03-08 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Simpson, Crawford and Simpson, 1890-01-07 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - Simpson, Crawford and Simpson, 1890-12-24 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Simpson, Crawford and Simpson, 1892-01-02 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Simpson, Crawford and Simpson, 1892-10-31 (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - Simpson, Crawford and Simpson, 1892-11-19 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Simpson, Robert Jr., 1886-05-24 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Simpson, Robert Jr., 1887-05-02 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Simpson, Robert Jr., 1887-05-05 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Simpson, Robert Jr., 1892-01-25 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Sitwell, Cecil, 1891-10-22 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Skinner, Henry, 1893-10-06 (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - Slaught, H.E.
    - Slingerland, Effie Earll, 1892-01-19 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      Mrs. Mark V. Slingerland
    - Slingerland, Mark Vernon, 1889-06-05 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Slingerland, Mark Vernon, 1889-06-22 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Slingerland, Mark Vernon, 1889-07-16 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Slingerland, Mark Vernon, 1889-08-23 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Slingerland, Mark Vernon, 1889-09-25 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Slingerland, Mark Vernon, 1889-10-23 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Slingerland, Mark Vernon, 1890-02-02 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Slingerland, Mark Vernon, 1890-03-02 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Slingerland, Mark Vernon, 1890-05-25 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Slingerland, Mark Vernon, 1890-06-07 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Slingerland, Mark Vernon, 1891-09-10 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Slingerland, Mark Vernon, 1891-09-16 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Slingerland, Mark Vernon, 1892-01-19 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Slingerland, Mark Vernon, 1900-06-30 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Smedie, J.M., 1886-05-24 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Smith, Albert W., 1890-04-28 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Smith, Albert W., 1891-05-18 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Smith, Arthur, 1890-04-30 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Smith, Arthur, Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Smith, B.H.E., 1887-10-21 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Smith, Charity, 1892-10-23 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Smith, Emily S., 1885-11-12 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Smith, Emily S., 1886-01-04 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Smith, Emory E., 1892-02-08 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Horticulturist
    - Smith, Emory E., 1892-02-22 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Smith, Emory E., 1892-02-27 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Smith, Eugene Allen, 1891-12-28 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Smith, Helen A., 1888-12-04 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Smith, Herbert Huntington, 1890-03-26 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Smith, Herbert Huntington, 1891-03-26 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Smith, Herbert Huntington, 1891-07-29 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Smith, Herbert Huntington, 1893-01-13 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Smith, Herbert Huntington, 1896-04-12 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Smith, Herbert Huntington, 1896-04-21 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Smith, Herbert Huntington, 1896-04-24 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Smith, Herbert Huntington, 1896-04-30 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Smith, Herbert Huntington, 1896-05-16 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Smith, Herbert Huntington, Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Smith, Herman Woodworth, 1890-08-13 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      Nova Scotia Agricultural College
    - Smith, Herman Woodworth, 1892-03-16 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Smith, John Bernhardt, 1885-05-28 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Smith, John Bernhardt, 1886-04-09 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Smith, John Bernhardt, 1887-07-26 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Smith, John Bernhardt, 1887-08-27 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Smith, John Bernhardt, 1890-08-04 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Smith, John Bernhardt, 1890-08-16 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Smith, John Bernhardt, 1890-09-12 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Smith, John Bernhardt, 1890-09-21 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Smith, John Bernhardt, 1891-07-08 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Smith, John Bernhardt, 1891-07-18 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Smith, John Bernhardt, 1891-07-30 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Smith, John Bernhardt, 1891-12-15 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Smith, John Bernhardt, 1891-12-22 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Smith, John Bernhardt, 1892-03-21 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Smith, John Bernhardt, 1892-05-05 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Smith, John Bernhardt, 1892-08-29 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Smith, John Bernhardt, 1892-09-28 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Smith, John Bernhardt, 1892-11-21 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Smith, John Bernhardt, 1892-11-28 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Smith, John Bernhardt, 1892-12-18 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Smith, John Bernhardt, 1893-10-18 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Smith, John Bernhardt, 1893-10-26 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Smith, John Bernhardt, 1893-11-04 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Smith, John Bernhardt, 1894-01-10 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Smith, John Bernhardt, 1894-01-18 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Smith, John Bernhardt, 1894-01-19 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Smith, John Bernhardt, 1894-01-25 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Smith, John Bernhardt, 1894-01-27 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Smith, John Bernhardt, 1894-01-30 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Smith, John Bernhardt, 1894-02-07 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Smith, John Bernhardt, 1894-09-13 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Smith, John Bernhardt, 1896-10-08 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Smith, L. Toulmin, 1891-10-01 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Smith, Margaret Keiver, 1892-11-14 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Smith, Oliver A., 1890-12-28 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Smith, Theobald, 1889-06-23 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      Comparative Pathologist
    - Smith, W and T, 1888-08-24 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      The Geneva Nursery
    - Smith, Wilbur Hazelton, 1887-10-15 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Snow, Benjamin Warner, 1888-07-23 (Box 2, Folder 32)
      Physics
    - Snow, Francis Huntington, 1884-07-02 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Snow, Francis Huntington, 1891-12-08 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Snow, Francis Huntington, 1893-08-15 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Snow, George C., 1891-05-14 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Snyder, Charles Earl, 1892-07-12 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Societe Entomologique De France, Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Society for Prevention of Crime, 1886-05-05 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Society of Naturalists, Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Socken, Osten, 1892-01-06 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      from Germany
    - Spalding, A.G. and Brothers, 1887-05-25 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      Manufacturers of guns and sporting goods
    - Spaulding, Alice M., 1886-06-01 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Spaulding, Alice M., 1886-06-08 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Speer, R.P., 1888-03-29 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Spence, R.E., 1890-06-20 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Sprague, Delos Everett, 1889-11-05 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Stanbrough, J.B., 1887-07-26 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Standinger and Haas, 1892-05-13 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Stanley, C.M., 1890-11-14 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Stanton, William Alfred, 1893-09-06 (Box 5, Folder 21)
      Architect
    - Stebbins, C.W., 1888-08-09 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      New York Experimental Station
    - Stebbins, C.W., Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Stecker, Herman, 1881-11-17 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Lepidopterist; Sculptor
    - Stecker, Herman, 1892-04-25 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Stedman, George L. Jr., 1888-06-14 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Stedman, George L. Jr., Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Stedman, John Moore, 1886-01-17 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Stedman, John Moore, 1886-01-24 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Stedman, John Moore, 1886-01-31 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Stedman, John Moore, 1886-02-07 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Stedman, John Moore, 1886-02-28 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Stedman, John Moore, 1886-03-07 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Stedman, John Moore, 1886-03-10 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Stedman, John Moore, 1886-03-14 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Stedman, John Moore, 1886-07-13 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Stedman, John Moore, 1887-03-20 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Stedman, John Moore, 1890-02-02 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Stedman, John Moore, 1890-02-11 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Stedman, John Moore, 1890-02-17 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Stedman, John Moore, 1890-09-04 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Stedman, John Moore, 1890-10-30 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Stedman, John Moore, 1891-02-01 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Stedman, John Moore, 1891-04-07 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Stedman, John Moore, 1891-04-23 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Stedman, John Moore, 1891-05-15 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Stedman, John Moore, 1891-05-19 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Stedman, John Moore, 1891-05-21 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Stedman, John Moore, 1891-10-19 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Stedman, John Moore, 1892-07-27 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Stedman, John Moore, 1893-10-27 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Stevens, F.L., 1891-08-18 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Stevens, Henry and Sons, 1896-10-01 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Stevens, Henry and Sons, 1896-10-16 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Stevens, Henry and Sons, 1896-10-23 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Stevens, Henry and Sons, 1896-10-30 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Stevens, Henry and Sons, 1897-05-17 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Stevens, Henry and Sons, 1897-05-31 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Stevens, Henry and Sons, 1897-07-10 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Stevenson, J.M., 1889-02-05 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Stewart and Collins, 1901-01-01 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Stewart, D.B. and Company, 1891-01-24 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Stewart, D.B. and Company, 1891-01-30 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Stewart, D.B. and Company, 1891-11-14 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Stewart, D.B. and Company, 1892-10-06 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Stewart, D.B. and Company, 1893-06-03 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Stewart, D.B. and Company, 1893-08-19 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Stewart, D.B. and Company, 1894-04-28 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Stiles, Charles Wardell, 1892-08-25 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      U.S. Dept. of Agriculture, Bureau of Animal Industry
    - Stoller, James Hough, 1894-01-13 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Stone, Dwight D., 1887-03-08 (Box 2, Folder 22)